Some thing is watching... waiting... and wanting on...
Saturn 3 is a science fiction, thriller film directed by Stanley Donen.
In the future, Earth is overcrowded and the
population relies on distant bases to be fed.
In the Saturn 3 station, Major Adam and the scientist Alex, who is also his lover and has never been on
Earth, have been researching hydroponics for three years in the base alone with their dog Sally.
Captain Benson arrives Saturn 3 with Hector, incapable to controlling his
emotions he transfers his homicidal tendency and insanity to Hector.
Now Major Adam and Alex are trapped in the station
with a dangerous psychopath robot.
Alex, played by Farrah Fawcett-Majors.
Major Adam, played by Kirk Douglas.
Benson, played by Harvey Keitel.
Harding (uncredited), played by Ed Bishop.
Benson (uncredited) (voice), played by Roy Dotrice.
Technician (uncredited), played by Stephanie English.
Saturn 3 is a 1980 British science fiction film produced and directed by Stanley
Donen, starring Farrah Fawcett, Kirk Douglas and Harvey Keitel.
The screenplay was written by Martin Amis, from a story by John Barry.
Though a British production, made by Lew Grade's ITC Entertainment and shot at
Shepperton Studios, the film has an American cast and director.
Saturn 3 was a box office bomb and earned largely negative reviews.
Keitel's biographer called the film the "nadir of his career".
The film explores themes of spacecraft, moon, chess, tattoo, cyborg.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.